So our next big O notation is O of one.
So let's start out with some code.
Here we have a function called add items, and all we're going to do is we're going to return n plus
n, There's only one operation here and that's the addition.
So it doesn't matter if N is one or n is a million, the number of operations is going to be one, and
that is O of one.
Well, what if we add.
Another edition.
Well, now, that's two operations, right?
O of two.
And as you may have guessed, we're going to simplify this and make it o of one.
So o of one a lot of times is referred to as constant time.
So this situation here where we have two additions.
It's two operations that is constant.
No matter what n is, the number of operations does not change as in changes.
So let's take a look at this on the graph.
Just a flat line across the bottom.
It is the most efficient o.
Nothing is more efficient than O of one.
Remember you will also hear this referred to as constant time.
So if you hear that phrase, that is o of one.